{
    "id": "32e7fb5ff7ff4787816aaa1bcd1e9e58",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Moments later the sun disappeared …………………. the horizon.",
            "description": "We prefer below when one thing is not directly under another.",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "below"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………….. at six while the roads were empty.",
            "description": "We do not use begin to talk about starting a journey.",
            "answers": [
                "began",
                "started",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are still …………………………",
            "description": "Underneath can only indicate physical position.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "underneath"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. three suspects have been arrested.",
            "description": "We can use either all or all the before a number.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We spend ………………………… weekends at our country cottage.",
            "description": "Alternate means every second.",
            "answers": [
                "alternate",
                "alternative",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ……………………….. it’s going to rain.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that she ………………………. told.",
            "description": "In British English, should is used before be in this structure. The structure without should is more common in American English.",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "should be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like two dozen mangoes ………………………..",
            "description": "Altogether can be used to give totals.",
            "answers": [
                "all together",
                "altogether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The committee …………………………. announced its decision.",
            "description": "Committee is a collective noun. In American English, collective nouns are always treated as singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will telephone you after I ……………………….",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to future.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Martha is a/an ……………………………. woman.",
            "description": "Afraid is not usually used before a noun in attributive position.",
            "answers": [
                "afraid",
                "frightened",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to do my exams, and ………………………. I’m going to study law.",
            "description": "After is not used alone as an adverb. Instead we use afterwards. ",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "afterwards",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}